Finding Aid for Philip A. Hart Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Legislative files, 1959-1976; 74 linear feet
  - Correspondence with government officials, organizations, and other public figures
    - Reuther, Walter (Box 75)
    - Richardson, Elliot (Box 75)
    - Rickover, H.G. (Box 75)
    - Romney, George (Box 75)
    - Scholle, August (Box 75)
    - Schultze, Charles L. (Box 75)
    - Shriver, Sargent (Box 75)
    - Shultz, George P. (Box 75)
    - Simon, William E. (Box 75)
    - Staebler, Neil (Box 75)
    - Stans, Maurice (Box 75)
    - Swainson, John (Box 75)
    - Truman, Harry S. (Box 75)
    - Udall, Stewart (Box 75)
    - Volpe, John A. (Box 75)
    - Wallace, George (Box 75)
    - Warren, Earl (Box 75)
    - Weaver, Robert C. (Box 75)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box 75)
    - Wilkins, Roy (Box 75)
    - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 75)
    - Woodcock, Leonard (Box 75)
    - Young, Coleman A. (Box 75)
- Staff files, 1959-1976; 20 linear feet
  The Staff Files (1959-1976; 20 linear ft.) were maintained by Hart's staff (except for the Press Office which is a separate series). Because of the complexity of legislative issues and constituent concerns, Hart had a staff of 7-10 people with another dozen or so working with the thousands of letters received each week and on other clerical tasks. This series consists of the files of many of the senior Hart staff, those with specific legislative or administrative responsibilities. Included are Hart's first administrative assistant, William B. Welch, his legislative counsel Donald F. Tucker, special assistant John M. (Jack) Cornman, legislative assistant Muriel Ferris among others. A complete list of individuals with papers in the Hart papers will be found in the Summary Contents List. A partial listing of all Hart staff members together with area of responsibility will be found in the Biographical/Personal series (box 1; folder, "Hart staff miscellanea/assignments").
  Because Hart relied so heavily on his staff, this series documents those issues and pieces of legislation about which Hart was most concerned. Included here are memoranda between Hart and his staff about the drafting of legislation and the strategy to be used in reaching a consensus so that any given bill might become law. Worthy of special mention is a subseries composed of the working files of various staff members. Arranged alphabetically, this subseries consists of memoranda, reports, and documents arranged topically. Large portions of this subseries relate to the amnesty issue, the Sleeping Bear Dunes and Pictures Rocks national parks legislation, the debate over control of automobile emissions, and the Seafarer/Sanguine project. An important part of this subseries is files of memoranda arranged chronologically on legislation and other public policy issues.
  - William B. Welch (Administrative Assistant)
    - Subject files
      - Atomic power reactor, 1959 (Box 76)
      - Civil rights
        - Election rights, 1959 (Box 76)
        - United States Commission on Civil Rights (J. Hannah), 1961-1963 (Box 76)
      - Consumer legislation, 1961 (Box 76)
      - Democratic National Committee, Research Division, 1960
        (Welch was Director of Research)
        - Africa (Box 76)
        - Atomic Energy (Box 76)
        - Campaign memoranda and correspondence (Box 76)
        - Campaign practices (Box 76)
        - Civil liberties (Box 76)
        - Education (Box 76)
        - Far East affairs (Box 76)
        - Health (Box 76)
        - Immigration and naturalization (Box 76)
        - Indians (Box 76)
        - Latin American policy (Box 76)
        - Nixon-Operation Harass (Box 76)
        - Religious issue (Box 76)
        - State briefing papers (Box 76)
      - Drugs: South American drug problem, 1963 (Box 76)
      - Economy of Michigan, 1959 (Box 76)
      - Federal excise taxes, 1961 (Box 76)
      - Food Act of 1960, 1959 (Box 76)
      - Food distribution program, 1959 (Box 76)
      - Government Contracts, Agencies and Properties, Subcommittee of the Task Force on Area Redevelopment Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 76)
        (Welch was staff director of subcommittee)
      - NASA: Saturn Launch Vehicle Contract, 1960 (Box 76)
      - Public Works Assistance Survey of Michigan municipalities, 1961; 2 folders (Box 76)
      - Refugees and Escapees Subcommittee, 1961 (Box 76)
      - Wheat crops, 1959-1960 (Box 76)
  - Muriel Ferris
    - Subject files
      - ABM (Sentinel anti-ballistic missile system), 1968-1970
        - 1968-1970, 10 folders (Box 76)
        - 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 77)
      - Agriculture (Box 77)
      - Airport legislation (Box 77)
      - Air pollution (Box 77)
      - Appalachia (Box 77)
        (Upper Great Lakes Development Amendment to Bill)
      - Aviation bill (Box 77)
      - Beans (Box 77)
      - Beef (Box 77)
      - Cherries (Box 77)
      - Cigarette bill (Box 77)
      - Consumer Subcommittee (Box 77)
      - Crime-Juvenile delinquency (Box 77)
      - Disarmament, 1959-1964 (Box 77)
      - Education
        - General, 2 folders (Box 77)
        - Opportunity Grant Program (Box 77)
        - Appropriations (Box 77)
        - Title I (ESEA) (Box 77)
      - Environment Subcommittee (Box 77)
      - Farm bills (Box 77)
      - Federal Insurance Guarantee Corporation (Box 77)
      - Fish, 3 folders (Box 77)
      - Fish bill
        - Wholesome Fish and Fishery Products Act of, 1969; 2 folders (Box 77)
      - Fish Inspection Bill
        - 1967 (Box 77)
        - 1971 (Box 77)
      - Fish and wildlife (Box 77)
      - Food (Box 77)
      - Foreign aid (Box 77)
      - Foreign policy (Box 77)
      - Forest
        - National (Box 78)
        - Michigan private roads (Box 78)
      - Great Lakes Basin Commission (Box 78)
      - Great Lakes-Lamprey eel, 1967-1968 (Box 78)
      - Health (Box 78)
      - Housing (Box 78)
      - Legislative Assistants meetings (Box 78)
      - Mass transit (Box 78)
      - Medicaid (Box 78)
      - Members of Congress for Peace Through Law (Box 78)
      - Milk (Box 78)
      - Multilateral Force (Box 78)
      - Nuclear Test Ban, 2 folders (Box 78)
      - Nutrition (Box 78)
      - Parks
        - Recreation Parkways, 1964-1965 (Box 78)
        - Wildlife areas-Isle Royale (Box 78)
      - Power-Rural Electrification Act (REA) (Box 78)
      - Pesticides (Box 78)
      - Pittman-Robertson Wildlife Program (Box 78)
      - Press Conference (Box 78)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 78)
      - Recreation, 2 folders (Box 78)
      - School Lunch Program
        - Appropriations (Box 78)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 78)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 78)
        - General (Box 78)
      - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1965-1969; 6 folders (Box 78)
      - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Television (CATV) (Box 79)
      - Trade
        - Automotive products (Canada-U.S.) (Box 79)
        - International, 1964-1970 (Box 79)
        - General (Box 79)
      - Transportation
        - Surface transportation (motor carriers) (Box 79)
        - Surface transportation (Box 79)
          (Repeal of section 22, ICC Act)
      - United Nations (Box 79)
      - Upper Great Lakes Regional Commission, 1966-1971 (Box 79)
      - Vietnam, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Vocational education (Box 79)
      - Water
        - 1969 (Box 79)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 79)
        - Boat sanitation (Box 79)
        - Grants (Box 79)
        - Lake Michigan (Box 79)
        - Legislation (Box 79)
        - Michigan (local problems) (Box 79)
        - Michigan Water Resources Commission (Box 79)
        - Senate Select Committee on Water Resources, 2 folders (Box 79)
        - Watershed (Box 79)
        - General (Box 79)
      - Watersheds (St. Joseph River) (Box 79)
      - Welfare (Box 79)
      - Women (Box 79)
      - Personal Files
        - President's Commission on the Status of Women, 4 folders (Box 79)
        - Equal pay for women (Box 79)
  - Donald F. Tucker (Legislative Counsel), 1973-1974
    - Subject files
      - Airlines
        - Inclusive Tour Charter Bill, S. 1739, 2 folders (Box 80)
      - Aviation
        - Foreign air fares (Box 80)
      - Defense
        - All volunteer army (Box 80)
        - Appropriations (Box 80)
        - B-1 Bomber (Box 80)
        - Budget (Box 80)
      - Energy
        - Consumer Energy Act (Box 80)
        - Crisis impact (Box 80)
        - Electrical appliances (Box 80)
        - Energy Emergency Standby Authorities, S. 3267 (Box 80)
        - Energy Information Act, S. 2782 (Box 80)
        - Energy Research and Development Administration, S. 2744 (Box 80)
        - Federal Energy Administration (Box 80)
        - Nuclear power plants (Box 80)
      - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan (Box 80)
      - Explosives, S. 2064 (Box 80)
      - Fertilizer shortage in Michigan (Box 80)
      - Fisheries (mesh gill nets) (Box 80)
      - Great Lakes Regional Center (Box 80)
      - Hawaii Dock Strike Bill, S. 1566 (Box 80)
      - Inflation (Box 80)
      - Insurance (national health insurance) (Box 80)
      - Isle Royale (Box 80)
      - Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Bill, S. 821 (Box 80)
      - Monroe (Mich.) sewage treatment project (Box 80)
      - NASA (large space telescope) (Box 80)
      - Public utilities financing (Box 80)
      - Railroads
        - Abandonment (Michigan) (Box 80)
        - Abandonment letters, 3 folders (Box 80)
        - AMTRAK (Roger Lewis nomination) (Box 80)
        - Ann Arbor railroad problem (Box 80)
        - Erie Lackawanna (Box 80)
        - Grain car shortage (Box 80)
      - Refugees
        - General (Box 80)
        - Chile (Box 80)
        - Political prisoners (Box 80)
        - Soviet Jewry (Box 80)
        - Vietnam discharges, S. 1715 (Box 80)
        - Vietnam MIAs and POWs (Box 80)
      - Silbert (E.J.) nomination as U.S. Attorney for Washington D.C. (Box 80)
      - Transportation
        - Surface (Box 80)
        - Upper Peninsula (Box 80)
      - Truckers strike, 1974 (Box 80)
      - Waterways
        - AuSable River (Box 81)
        - Barge - Mixing Rule (Box 81)
        - Sea Grant Authorization (Box 81)
      - Women
        - Sex discrimination (Kalamazoo School) (Box 81)
        - Sex discrimination (NASA) (Box 81)
        - Sex discrimination (General) (Box 81)
  - Burt Wides
    - Subject files
      - Consumer Protection Act, 1970 (Box 81)
      - Judicial nominations (Box 81)
      - Product safety material (Box 81)
      - Supreme Court (Box 81)
  - Peggy Crenshaw
    - Subject files
      - Federal Communications Commission (Fogerty and White nominations) (Box 81)
      - Great Lakes (Box 81)
      - Labor
        - Closing of Ford Rouge plant (Box 81)
        - Farm labor problems (Box 81)
        - Hatch Act (H.R. 8617S. 372) (Box 81)
        - Opportunities Industrialization Centers (OIC), S. 2939 (Box 81)
        - Situs picketing and collective bargaining (Box 81)
        - Teamsters (Box 81)
        - White Pine Copperage Mine (Box 81)
      - Legal service (Box 81)
      - Press gallery problems (Box 81)
      - Tugboat "Barbara Ann" (private case) (Box 81)
      - Xm-1 tank (Box 81)
  - John M. (Jack) Cornman (Special Assistant)
    - Subject files
      - Agriculture (Box 81)
      - Animals-humane treatment (Box 81)
      - Appropriations (Box 81)
      - Au Sable (Box 81)
      - Automobile emissions (Box 81)
      - Busing, 1972-1973 (Box 81)
      - Cambodia (Box 81)
      - Campaign spending (Box 81)
      - Chrysler tax situation, 1975 (Box 81)
      - Crime (Box 81)
      - Detroit (IRS Data Center) (Box 81)
      - Detroit Public Health Service (Box 81)
      - Draft (Box 81)
      - Education in Michigan (Box 81)
      - Forests
        - General (Box 81)
        - Big-Sea Water National Forest Recreation Area (Box 81)
        - Black River Recreation Area (Box 81)
        - Sylvania Recreation Area (Box 81)
      - Grand River Basin Comprehensive Water Resources Planning Study (Box 82)
      - Great Lakes
        - Lamprey eel (Box 82)
      - Hart-Scott Antitrust Improvements Act (Box 82)
      - HEW appropriations (health) (Box 82)
      - Health Security Act, 1971 (Box 82)
      - Housing, 11 folders (Box 82)
      - Inflation; unemployment (Box 82)
      - Interior appropriations (Box 82)
      - Job Corps (Box 82)
      - Labor; Health, Education and Welfare, 1971 (Box 82)
      - Mass transit (Box 82)
      - MIAs-POWs (Box 82)
      - Military spending, 1973 (Box 82)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1973 (Box 82)
      - Oil imports (Box 82)
      - Passenger railroads (Box 82)
      - Pension (Box 82)
      - Pension plans (Box 82)
      - Political prisoners, 2 folders (Box 82)
      - Priorities (Box 82)
      - Public utilities (Box 82)
      - Public Works
        - 1961 (Box 83)
        - 1972 (Box 83)
        - Appropriations (Box 83)
      - Refugees (Cuban) (Box 83)
      - Soil Conservation Service (Box 83)
      - Tax bill (Box 83)
      - Transportation appropriations (Box 83)
      - Unemployment (Box 83)
      - Urban Bank (Box 83)
      - Urban Mass Transportation Act, S. 3154 (Box 83)
      - Vladivostok Agreement and NPR Act, 1975 (Box 83)
      - Watergate, 1973 (Box 83)
  - Mildred Wade (Legislative Assistant)
    - Health and education subject files, 0.42 linear feet (Box 83)
  - Arnaldo Martinez
    - Coalition of Eastern Native Americans (Box 83)
    - Federal Property and Administration Services Act of, 1949 (Box 83)
  - W. Harrison Welford
    - A-Z (Box 84)
  - Lorie Barnett
    - Topical files (unprocessed) (Box 85)
  - Various staff working files
    (arranged alphabetically by topic)
    - Air transportation, 5 folders (Box 85)
    - Amnesty, 0.5 linear feet (Box 85)
    - Automobile and automobile emissions, 0.75 linear feet (Box 86)
    - Banking, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Commerce Committee, 5 folders (Box 86)
    - Consumer affairs, 6 folders (Box 87)
    - Energy, 0.42 linear feet (Box 87)
    - Energy-Oil and gas divestiture, 0.33 linear feet (Box 87)
    - Environment, 0.25 linear feet (Box 87)
    - Environment, 0.33 linear feet (Box 88)
    - Housing, 5 folders (Box 88)
    - Justice (outline notes for Public Justice conference) (Box 88)
    - Memoranda, 1967-1976; 14 folders (Box 88)
    - Regulatory reform, 4 folders (Box 88)
    - Seafarer/Sanguine, 24 folders (Box 89)
    - Sleeping Bear Dunes/Pictured Rocks, etc., 14 folders (Box 89)
    - Sports-Amateur Athletics Act, 1973-1974 (Box 89)
    - Tax reform, 1974 (Box 89)
    - Transport-Mass Transit Act, 1975 (Box 89)
  - Office working and reference files, circa 1959-1965
    (mainly files of William Welch)
    - Administrative practices (Box 90)
    - Agriculture (Box 90)
    - Anti-Trust and Monopoly Subcommittee (Box 90)
    - Area Redevelopment (Box 90)
    - Atomic energy (Box 91)
    - Atomic power (Box 91)
    - Aviation (Box 91)
    - Budget (Box 91)
    - Civil liberties (Box 91)
    - Civil rights (Box 91)
      (Voting Rights Act, S. 1564)
    - Civil rights (reapportionment), 1964-1965 (Box 92)
    - Civil rights (miscellaneous) (Box 92)
    - Civil rights (miscellaneous) (Box 93)
    - Communications (Box 93)
    - Cooperatives (Box 93)
    - District of Columbia (Box 93)
    - Economics (Box 93)
    - Education (Box 93)
    - Elections (Box 93)
    - Federal-state relations (Box 93)
    - Foreign policy (Box 93)
    - Forests and forestry (Box 93)
    - Government organization (Box 94)
    - Health (Box 94)
    - Housing and community planning (Box 94)
    - Immigration (Box 94)
    - Indians (Box 94)
    - Judicial (Box 94)
    - Juvenile delinquency (Box 94)
    - Labor (Box 94)
    - Michigan (Box 94)
    - Mining (Box 94)
    - National defense (Box 95)
    - Natural resources (Box 95)
    - Patents (Box 95)
    - Politics (Box 95)
    - Post Office (Box 95)
    - Power (Box 95)
    - Public works (Box 95)
    - Railroads (Box 95)
    - Refugees and escapees (Box 95)
    - Science and space (Box 95)
    - Small business (Box 95)
    - Social Security (Box 95)
    - Tariffs and trade (Box 95)
    - Taxes (Box 95)
    - Transportation (Box 95)
    - United Nations (Box 95)
    - Veterans (Box 95)
    - War claims (Box 95)
    - Water (Box 95)
    - Welfare (Box 95)
    - Women (Box 95)
- Press Office, 1959-1976; 38 linear feet
  Because of the character of its work and the types of material it maintained, the Press Office (1959-1976; 38 linear feet) is treated differently from the rest of the Hart staff files. The Press Office series consists of five major subseries: "Press releases and newsletters," "Speeches," "Newspaper clippings," "Subject files" and "Schedules." Except for the "Subject files," each of the subseries has been arranged chronologically. The first two subseries are comprised of mimeographed releases of press notices, newsletters, and speeches given. "Clippings" consists of newspaper clippings compiled by a professional clipping service about Hart and his congressional activities. This series reflects and documents Hart's image of himself and the image that the print media had of him. The "Subject files" comprise press releases, memoranda, drafts, and other information maintained by Hart's press secretary Jerry Kabel. These files are arranged alphabetically by broad subject heading and should be used to complement other subject files within the collection.
  - Press releases and newsletters
    - 1959-May 1960 (Box 96)
    - June 1960-June 1961 (Box 97)
    - July 1961-July 1962 (Box 98)
    - August 1962-May 1963 (Box 99)
    - June 1963-March 1964 (Box 100)
    - April 1964-March 1965 (Box 101)
    - April 1965-April 1966 (Box 102)
    - May 1966-August 1967 (Box 103)
    - September 1967-November 1968 (Box 104)
    - December 1968-July 1969 (Box 105)
    - August 1969-June 1970 (Box 106)
    - July 1970-December 1971 (Box 107)
    - January 1972-April 1974 (Box 108)
    - April 1974-November 1976 (Box 109)
  - Speeches
    - 1958-1968 (Box 110)
    - 1969-1976 (Box 111)
    - Undated (Box 111)
    - Undated (Box 112)
      (continued)
    - Miscellaneous subjects (Box 112)
    - Re military topics (Box 112)
    - Re environment and consumer affairs (Box 112)
    - Re anti-trust legislation (Box 112)
    - Re civil and human rights (Box 112)
    - Senate floor statements, 1959; 1965-1976 (Box 112)
    - Radio scripts (drafts) (Box 112)
    - TV scripts (drafts) (Box 112)
    - TV interviews (transcripts) (Box 112)
    - TV appearances (briefing material) (Box 112)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - October 1958-1959 (Box 113)
    - 1960-May 1961 (Box 114)
    - June-November 1961 (Box 115)
    - December 1961-June 1962 (Box 116)
    - July 1962-March 1963 (Box 117)
    - April-September 1963 (Box 118)
    - October 1963-February 1964 (Box 119)
    - March-June 1964 (Box 120)
    - July-December 1964 (Box 121)
    - [not received], 1965-1967 (Box 122)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 122)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 123)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 124)
    - 1972 (Box 125)
    - 1973 (Box 126)
    - 1974 (Box 127)
    - 1975 (Box 128)
    - 1976 (Box 129)
  - Subject files
    (mainly press releases and other files of Jerry Kabel)
    - ABM (Box 130)
    - Agriculture (Box 130)
    - Busing (Box 130)
    - Capital punishment (Box 130)
    - Captive nations (Box 130)
    - Cherries (Box 130)
    - Civil disorders (riots) (Box 130)
    - Civil rights, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Commerce Subcommittee (Box 130)
    - Crime (Box 130)
    - Cuban refugees (Box 130)
    - Defense (Box 130)
    - Economic issues (Box 130)
    - Education (Box 130)
    - Energy Divestiture, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Great Lakes (Box 130)
    - Health and welfare (Box 130)
    - Housing and urban problems (Box 130)
    - Immigration (Box 130)
    - Import quota (Box 130)
    - International issues (Box 130)
    - Natural gas (Box 130)
    - Olympics (Box 131)
    - Pesticides (Box 131)
    - Political (Box 131)
    - Political ethics (Box 131)
    - Pollution (Box 131)
    - Presidential primaries (Box 131)
    - Refugees (Box 131)
    - Selective Service (Box 131)
    - Senate Rule 22 (Box 131)
    - Sleeping Bear Dunes/Pictured Rocks (Box 131)
    - Supreme Court (Box 131)
    - Truth-in-lending (Box 131)
    - Truth-in-packaging (Box 131)
    - Vietnam (Box 131)
    - Violence Commission (Box 131)
    - Voting age (Box 131)
    - War on Poverty (Box 131)
    - Welfare (Box 131)
  - Articles
    - Various, 3 folders (Box 131)
  - Radio-TV scripts
    - Various, 3 folders (Box 131)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence
      - Jerry Kabel (Personal File), 1970-1971 (Box 132)
      - Robo Letters (Form Letters), 1963-1968 (Box 132)
      - Robo Letters (Form Letters), 1969 (Box 132)
    - Legislative Proposals, 1968-1969 (Box 132)
    - Memoranda (Box 132)
    - Miscellaneous Materials, 2 folders
      - 1963-1968 (Box 132)
      - 1969-1976 (Box 132)
    - Press Conference Notes, 4 folders
      - 1967-1968 (Box 132)
      - 1969 (Box 132)
      - 1971 (Box 132)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 132)
    - Public Statements, 1968-1975 (Box 132)
    - Topical File, 5 folders
      - Abe Fortas Case (clippings), 1969 (Box 132)
      - Antitrust Bill, 1976 (Box 132)
      - Diet Pill Hearings, 1968 (Box 132)
      - Jane Hart (Mrs. Philip A. Hart) Arrest (clippings), 1969 (Box 132)
      - Nixon Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 132)
  - Schedules
    - Dated files (Box 133)
- Subject files, 1959-1976; 96 linear feet
  The largest series within the collection, Subject Files (1959-1976; 96 linear ft.) contains correspondence, petitions, memoranda, and other documents, primarily illustrating the role of a U.S. Senator as an ombudsman between the citizens of his state (and often out-of-state) and their federal government. Though Subject Files is a constituent file, it is different from the Constituent Correspondence (described below) in that here there are detailed and individual responses from Hart or the appropriate government agency to citizen concerns. The files are arranged chronologically (except for the first five years of his tenure which is one alphabetical subseries), and then alphabetically by subject. The subject headings are broad, then further subdivided into specific subheadings. A typical kind of document exchange might include a letter from a constituent expressing a concern about a government service or the need for more or less government regulation or legislation. Hart and his staff respond to the letter, and where appropriate pass the letter along to the appropriate agency. The agency then responds to the constituent and includes a copy of the response for Hart and his files. Subject Files is different from Constituent Correspondence in that fewer form letters are used as responses and that the response is a specific reply to a concern and not usually a general statement of Hart's position on various issues.
  - 1959-1964
    - Agriculture
      - ACP Huron County, 1961-1962 (Box 134)
      - ACP Service, 1961 (Box 134)
      - ASC Comm. Newsletters from counties, 1962 (Box 134)
      - ASC Service, 1962-1963 (Box 134)
      - Agricultural Farm Program, Price Supports, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 134)
      - Agricultural Marketing Service, 1950-1964 (Box 134)
      - Apples, 1959-1962 (Box 134)
      - Beans, 1962-1963 (Box 134)
      - Beans, Maturity date, dry beans, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Beans, Soy Beans, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Beans, Surplus, 1962-1963 (Box 134)
      - Bird-depredations Control, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Census, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Cherries, 1960-1962 (Box 134)
      - Cherries, Exports, 1963 (Box 134)
      - Cherries, Farm Program Insurance Crop, 1963 (Box 134)
      - Cherries Crop, 1964 (Box 134)
      - Cherries, Frozen Pies, 1963 (Box 134)
      - Cherries, Publicity Favorable, 1963 (Box 134)
      - Cherries, Publicity Unfavorable, 1963 (Box 134)
      - Coffee, International Agreement, 1963-1964 (Box 134)